New England Medical Center Records MS099
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Departments, 1908 -- 1987; MS099.004; 49.2 Linear Feet
  - Pathology, 1970 -- 1982; MS099.004.008; 2.4 Linear Feet
    - Curriculum, 1979; MS099.004.008.036.00023 (Box 36)
    - Breast Clinic protocol, 1980; MS099.004.008.036.00024 (Box 36)
    - Progress reports, 1978; MS099.004.008.036.00025 (Box 36)
    - Site visits, 1978; MS099.004.008.036.00026 (Box 36)
    - C and E, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.008.036.00027 (Box 36)
    - Physician administrative meetings, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.004.008.036.00028 (Box 36)
    - M and D 8 floor plan, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.004.008.036.00029 (Box 36)
    - Blueprint - Pathology offices, laboratories, 1970; MS099.004.008.036.00030 (Box 36)
    - Departmental program objectives, 1980; MS099.004.008.036.00031 (Box 36)
    - C and E, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.008.036.00032 (Box 36)
    - Photographs, MS099.004.008.036.00033 (Box 36)
      Folder contains seperation sheet.
    - Departmental organization and procedure manuals, 1980 -- 1982; MS099.004.008.036.00034 (Box 36)
    - Expense account codes, 1980; MS099.004.008.037.00001 (Box 37)
    - Photo statistics, 1971 -- 1981; MS099.004.008.037.00002 (Box 37)
    - Department of professional income, 1978 -- 1979; MS099.004.008.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Pharmacy, 1970 -- 1987; MS099.004.009; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains publications and reports of the NEMC Pharmacy.
    - Formularies, 1984 -- 1986; MS099.004.009.037.00004 (Box 37)
    - Residency programs, 1974 -- 1980; MS099.004.009.037.00005 (Box 37)
    - The Forum, 1974 -- 1987; MS099.004.009.037.00006 (Box 37)
    - Rx hospital pharmacy notes, 1982 -- 1987; MS099.004.009.037.00007 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda, 1974 -- 1987; MS099.004.009.037.00008 (Box 37)
    - Report and recommendations on pharmaceutical services, 1970; MS099.004.009.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Social Work Services, 1908 -- 1980; MS099.004.010; 13.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains the administrative files of the department of Social Services, an office established in 1908 at the Boston Dispensary and later absorbed by the New England Medical Center. Social Work Services provided medical and psychological support for patients' illness related problems and assisted in their transition back into society.
    The early records are primarily those of the Director's office and include annual and special reports, correspondence, and minutes of departmental committees. Financial reports are from the central office as well as the Registrar. Later records include reports on social service, publications, press releases, and news clippings of important individuals. Case files of patients are well represented in this sub-series.
    According to Dave Nathan's Guide to the NEMC Archives, administrator's records from the Boston Dispensary, as well as reports from the Social Department, are missing.
    This sub-series is arranged into two groups, the Boston Dispensary and the New England Medical Center. Within each group, administrator's records are followed by individual case files. In the Boston Dispensary group, case files are first arranged by case number, then alphabetically. In the New England Medical Center group, case files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Boston Dispensary, 1908 -- 1970; MS099.004.010.001
      - Manual of policies and procedures relating to the admission of patients and to clinics and special services, 1942; MS099.004.010.037.00010 (Box 37)
      - Procedures - memos and reports, 1948 -- 1954; MS099.004.010.037.00011 (Box 37)
      - Boston Dispensary Social Service Department Policy Book, 1927; MS099.004.010.037.00012; Emerson, Ruth V. (Box 37)
      - Policies, rules and regulations of the Boston Dispensary and Social Service department, 1916; MS099.004.010.037.00013 (Box 37)
      - Treatment at the Dispensary, 1913; MS099.004.010.037.00014 (Box 37)
      - Boston Dispensary Social Service Department Policy Book, 1927; MS099.004.010.037.00015; Emerson, Ruth V. (Box 37)
      - BD Social Service policy, procedures, and organization, 1933 -- 1934; MS099.004.010.037.00016 (Box 37)
      - Massachusetts Department of Public Welfare sample forms, 1960 -- 1970; MS099.004.010.037.00017 (Box 37)
      - Social Service miscellaneous funds for patients correspondence, 1958 -- 1964; MS099.004.010.037.00018 (Box 37)
      - Social Service statistics, 1962; MS099.004.010.037.00019 (Box 37)
      - Portion of a study of fifty dependent families receiving mothers' aid in which medical problems appear, a case study of 10 families, 1961; MS099.004.010.037.00020; Frey, Helen (Box 37)
      - One month survey of the children's clinic at the Boston Dispensary, 1920; MS099.004.010.037.00021; Emerson, Ruth V. (Box 37)
      - Social Services and South End Diet Kitchen report, 1928; MS099.004.010.037.00022 (Box 37)
      - Home Medical Service report, 1940; MS099.004.010.037.00023 (Box 37)
      - Report on social aspects of medical care, 1943; MS099.004.010.037.00024 (Box 37)
      - Reports on Rheabilitaiton Institute, 1958; MS099.004.010.037.00025 (Box 37)
      - The parolee normal volunteer in clinical research, 1960; MS099.004.010.037.00026 (Box 37)
      - Study of medical, social, and psychological needs of a group of multiple sclerosis patients, 1964 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.037.00027; Bluestone, Joanne; Fleming, Marie; McMahon, Arthur; Wasserman, Herbert; Wein, Janet (Box 37)
      - Minutes of staff/medical conferences, 1912 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.037.00028 (Box 37)
      - Instructions in regard to Social Service records, 1948; MS099.004.010.037.00029 (Box 37)
      - Case files 200-3224, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.037.00030 (Box 37)
        Non-consecutive.
      - Case files 3350-8225, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.037.00031 (Box 37)
      - Case files 8375-9625, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.037.00032 (Box 37)
      - Case files 9400-11000, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00001 (Box 38)
      - Case files 11125-11900, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00002 (Box 38)
      - Case files 12150-13950, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00003 (Box 38)
      - Case files 14476-15000, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00004 (Box 38)
      - Case files 15100-15924, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00005 (Box 38)
      - Case files 17001-17234, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00006 (Box 38)
      - Case files 17243-17348, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00007 (Box 38)
      - Case files 17356-17402, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.038.00008 (Box 38)
      - Case files 17408-17499, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00001 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17501-17577, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00002 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17580-17675, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00003 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17681-17759, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00004 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17760-17783, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00005 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17782-17807, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00006 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17811-17822, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.039.00007 (Box 39)
      - Case files 17808-17839, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00001 (Box 40)
      - Case files 17840-17860, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00002 (Box 40)
      - Case files 17862-17879, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00003 (Box 40)
      - Case files 17880-17957, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00004 (Box 40)
      - Case files 18007-18032, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00005 (Box 40)
      - Case files, A, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00006 (Box 40)
      - Case files, B, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00007 (Box 40)
      - Case files, C, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00008 (Box 40)
      - Case files, D, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.040.00009 (Box 40)
      - Case files, E, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00001 (Box 41)
      - Case files, F, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00002 (Box 41)
      - Case files, G, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00003 (Box 41)
      - Case files, H, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00004 (Box 41)
      - Case files, I, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00005 (Box 41)
      - Case files, K, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00006 (Box 41)
      - Case files, L, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00007 (Box 41)
      - Case files, M, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00008 (Box 41)
      - Case files, N, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00009 (Box 41)
      - Case files, O, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00010 (Box 41)
      - Case files, P, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.041.00011 (Box 41)
      - Case files, Q, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00001 (Box 42)
      - Case files, R, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00002 (Box 42)
      - Case files, S, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00003 (Box 42)
      - Case files, T, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00004 (Box 42)
      - Case files, U, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00005 (Box 42)
      - Case files, V, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00006 (Box 42)
      - Case files, W, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00007 (Box 42)
      - Case files, Y, 1908 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.042.00008 (Box 42)
    - New England Medical Center, 1938 -- 1980; MS099.004.010.002
      - Social Service department annual reports, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.004.010.042.00009 (Box 42)
      - Memorandums Social Service department, 1972 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.042.00010 (Box 42)
      - NEMCH Social Service summer camp placement report, 1967 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.042.00011 (Box 42)
      - Disaster plan, 1973 -- 1976; MS099.004.010.042.00012 (Box 42)
      - Social Service - History of the Boston Dispensary manuscript, 1965 -- 1966; MS099.004.010.042.00013 (Box 42)
      - History of the Boston Dispensary manuscript, 1978; MS099.004.010.042.00014; Wire, Janet (Box 42)
      - Social Service department peer review minutes, 1973 -- 1976; MS099.004.010.042.00015 (Box 42)
      - Boston Chinese Community Health Service - Yuen's report, 1973; MS099.004.010.042.00016 (Box 42)
      - Boston Chinese Community Health Sercvice Social Services reports, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00017 (Box 42)
      - BCCHS - minutes of board meetings and directors reports, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00018 (Box 42)
      - Canotnese classes, 1973; MS099.004.010.042.00019 (Box 42)
      - Children and youth Chinese mental health team Tufts Mental Health A.B., 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00020 (Box 42)
      - List of interpreters, Chinese speaking, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00021 (Box 42)
      - American Health Congress, 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00022 (Box 42)
      - Resources for Chinese, 1971 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.042.00023 (Box 42)
      - BCCHS memorandum, 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00024 (Box 42)
      - Interpreting services, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00025 (Box 42)
      - Chinese Affairs Liaison Hospital, 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00026 (Box 42)
      - Nursing - Inservice Chinese, 1974; MS099.004.010.042.00027 (Box 42)
      - Psychistric In-patient and Day Hospital, 1973; MS099.004.010.042.00028 (Box 42)
      - Questionnaire interpreters, 1970; MS099.004.010.042.00029 (Box 42)
      - Social Service department funds for patients, 1977; MS099.004.010.042.00030 (Box 42)
      - Social Service department social research, 1973; MS099.004.010.042.00031 (Box 42)
      - Social Service department social work position description, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.004.010.042.00032 (Box 42)
      - Social Service department summer camp program, 1977; MS099.004.010.042.00033 (Box 42)
      - PSRO - Barbara Berkman, 1966 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.043.00001 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department applications and resumes, 1968 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.043.00002 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department monthly statistics, 1974 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00003 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department memorandum and reports, 1972 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00004 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department patient education and care, 1974; MS099.004.010.043.00005 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department unit meeting minutes, 1975 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00006 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department personnel policy, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.043.00007 (Box 43)
      - Ambulatory Social Service department annual report, 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00008 (Box 43)
      - Social Service department monthly statistics, 1976; MS099.004.010.043.00009 (Box 43)
      - Executive committee minutes - Social Service department, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.043.00010 (Box 43)
      - Tufts/NECH Clinical Research Unit, 1960; MS099.004.010.043.00011 (Box 43)
      - NEMCH Social Service department funds for patients, correspondence, 1965 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00012 (Box 43)
      - Social Service - Pediatrics, 1968 -- 1969; MS099.004.010.043.00013 (Box 43)
      - Pediatric Unit, 1975 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00014 (Box 43)
      - Pediatric Social Service, 1970 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.043.00015 (Box 43)
      - Taxi fares, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00016 (Box 43)
      - Taxi fares, 1972 -- 1976; MS099.004.010.043.00017 (Box 43)
      - Multiple sclerosis study, 1964 -- 1965; MS099.004.010.043.00018 (Box 43)
      - Consultation services, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00019 (Box 43)
      - Transportation, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00020 (Box 43)
      - Postage, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00021 (Box 43)
      - Books, dues and publications, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00022 (Box 43)
      - Dietary, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00023 (Box 43)
      - Material distribution, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00024 (Box 43)
      - Office and general supply, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00025 (Box 43)
      - Uniforms and linens, 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00026 (Box 43)
      - Other costs, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00027 (Box 43)
      - Advertisements, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00028 (Box 43)
      - Photocopying and xeroxing, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00029 (Box 43)
      - Transportation money, 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00030 (Box 43)
      - Telephone charges and calls, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00031 (Box 43)
      - Other telephone costs, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00032 (Box 43)
      - Repairs, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00033 (Box 43)
      - Outside repair requisitions, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00034 (Box 43)
      - Educational assistance program, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00035 (Box 43)
      - Continuing care expenses, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00036 (Box 43)
      - Parking fund requests, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00037 (Box 43)
      - Weber Fund, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00038 (Box 43)
      - 500 Fund, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00039 (Box 43)
      - Seminar, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00040 (Box 43)
      - American Cancer Society, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00041 (Box 43)
      - Social Service Fund, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00042 (Box 43)
      - Search committee, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00043 (Box 43)
      - Christmas Fund, 1969 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00044 (Box 43)
      - Medicare Technician Aide Program, 1978 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.043.00045 (Box 43)
      - Freeze related material, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00046 (Box 43)
      - Case worker evaluations, 1976; MS099.004.010.043.00047 (Box 43)
      - Consultation - Dr. Berkman, 1973 -- 1976; MS099.004.010.043.00048 (Box 43)
      - Chinese community, social service committee for Chinese community, 1970 -- 1972; MS099.004.010.043.00049 (Box 43)
      - Budget correspondence, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.043.00050 (Box 43)
      - Symposium committee, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00051 (Box 43)
      - Social Service departments elsewhere, 1976 -- 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00052 (Box 43)
      - Charities - funds, 1950 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.043.00053 (Box 43)
      - Symposium luncheon, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00054 (Box 43)
      - Symposium - correspondence, 1978; MS099.004.010.043.00055 (Box 43)
      - Supervisory seminar, 1977; MS099.004.010.043.00056 (Box 43)
      - Social work intern information, 1968 -- 1972; MS099.004.010.044.00001 (Box 44)
      - Supervisor's meetings, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.044.00002 (Box 44)
      - Social Service - departmental statistics, 1972 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.044.00003 (Box 44)
      - Annual report, 1973 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.044.00004 (Box 44)
      - Social work salary information, 1977; MS099.004.010.044.00005 (Box 44)
      - Social service personnel policies - salaries, benefits, 1967 -- 1972; MS099.004.010.044.00006 (Box 44)
      - Social service highlights, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.004.010.044.00007 (Box 44)
      - Highlight - Social Service department, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.044.00008 (Box 44)
      - Social service highlights, 1970 -- 1972; MS099.004.010.044.00009 (Box 44)
      - Social Service - Saturday coverage, 1966 -- 1967; MS099.004.010.044.00010 (Box 44)
      - Social Service - history of in-patient, 1938 -- 1964; MS099.004.010.044.00011 (Box 44)
      - Social Service nutrition affiliation material, 1966 -- 1974; MS099.004.010.044.00012 (Box 44)
      - Annual reports, 1966 -- 1975; MS099.004.010.044.00013 (Box 44)
      - Case files, A, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00014 (Box 44)
      - Case files, C, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00015 (Box 44)
      - Case files, D, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00016 (Box 44)
      - Case files, F, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00017 (Box 44)
      - Case files, G, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00018 (Box 44)
      - Case files, H, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00019 (Box 44)
      - Case files, K, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00020 (Box 44)
      - Case files, M, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00021 (Box 44)
      - Case files, O, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00022 (Box 44)
      - Case files, P, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00023 (Box 44)
      - Case files, R, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.044.00024 (Box 44)
      - Case files, S, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.045.00001 (Box 45)
      - Case files, T, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.045.00002 (Box 45)
      - Case files, W, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.045.00003 (Box 45)
      - Case files, X, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.045.00004 (Box 45)
      - Case files, Z, 1965 -- 1979; MS099.004.010.045.00005 (Box 45)
      - Boston Dispensary Home Care Service, 1958 -- 1961; MS099.004.010.045.00006 (Box 45)
      - Case files and correspondence regarding Clinical Study Unit (1 of 5), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.045.00007 (Box 45)
      - Case files and correspondence regarding Clinical Study Unit (2 of 5), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.045.00008 (Box 45)
      - Case files and correspondence regarding Clinical Study Unit (3 of 5), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.045.00009 (Box 45)
      - Case files and correspondence regarding Clinical Study Unit (4 of 5), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.045.00010 (Box 45)
      - Case files and correspondence regarding Clinical Study Unit (5 of 5), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.045.00011 (Box 45)
      - Case files, B, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.045.00012 (Box 45)
      - Case files, C, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00001 (Box 46)
      - Case files, D, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00002 (Box 46)
      - Case files, F, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00003 (Box 46)
      - Case files, G, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00004 (Box 46)
      - Case files, H, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00005 (Box 46)
      - Case files, J, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00006 (Box 46)
      - Case files, K, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00007 (Box 46)
      - Case files, L, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00008 (Box 46)
      - Case files, M, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00009 (Box 46)
      - Case files, N, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00010 (Box 46)
      - Case files, O, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00011 (Box 46)
      - Case files, P, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00012 (Box 46)
      - Case files, R, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.046.00013 (Box 46)
      - Case files, S, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.047.00001 (Box 47)
      - Case files, T, 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.047.00002 (Box 47)
      - Case files, W (1 of 2), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.047.00003 (Box 47)
      - Case files, W (2 of 2), 1950 -- 1978; MS099.004.010.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - Surgery, 1921 -- 1982; MS099.004.011; 27.6 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains registers of the NEMC Surgery department. These registers are detailed log books of individual surgeries, and include the patient's name, age, their preoperative diagnosis, the surgery performed, the time it was performed, and the attending surgeons, assistants, and nurses. Records of pediatric procedures from 1931 to 1949 are found in the Dispensary logs for those years. No records of Pratt Clinic procedures from 1938 to 1949 are extant. This sub-series has been restricted because it contains patient information.
    According to Dave Nathan's Guide to the NEMC archives, 4 volumes of pediatric logs from the Boston Dispensary and 1 log from the Farnsworth building (Volume 43) are missing.
    This sub-series is arranged into two groups, Operating room logs and Recovery room logs. These items are arranged by location, then date.
    - Operating room, 1921 -- 1982; MS099.004.011.001
      - Boston Dispensary, 1921-01-03 -- 1932-02-27; MS099.004.011.047.00005 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary, 1932-06-01 -- 1936-08-01; MS099.004.011.047.00006 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary, 1936-08-21 -- 1940-06-27; MS099.004.011.047.00007 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary, 1940-07-01 -- 1945-08-31; MS099.004.011.047.00008 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary, 1945-09-09 -- 1948-12-28; MS099.004.011.047.00009 (Box 47)
      - Operations - major cases, 1936-08-21 -- 1939-07-12; MS099.004.011.047.00010 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1970-04-28 -- 1970-12-22; MS099.004.011.047.00011 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1970-12-23 -- 1971-08-05; MS099.004.011.047.00012 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1971-08-05 -- 1972-03-27; MS099.004.011.047.00013 (Box 47)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1972-11-01 -- 1973-05-31; MS099.004.011.048.00001 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1973-06-01 -- 1973-12-31; MS099.004.011.048.00002 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1974-01-02 -- 1974-07-31; MS099.004.011.048.00003 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1974-08-01 -- 1975-03-21; MS099.004.011.048.00004 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1975-03-24 -- 1975-10-25; MS099.004.011.048.00005 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1975-10-24 -- 1976-05-18; MS099.004.011.048.00006 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1976-05-19 -- 1976-12-28; MS099.004.011.048.00007 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1976-12-29 -- 1977-06-10; MS099.004.011.048.00008 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1977-06-10 -- 1978-01-31; MS099.004.011.048.00009 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1978-01-31 -- 1978-08-16; MS099.004.011.048.00010 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1978-08-17 -- 1979-03-20; MS099.004.011.048.00011 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1979-03-20 -- 1979-10-09; MS099.004.011.048.00012 (Box 48)
      - Boston Dispensary register of operations, 1980-04-11 -- 1980-09-09; MS099.004.011.048.00013 (Box 48)
      - Farnsworth building register of operations, 1949-05-31 -- 1950-07-28; MS099.004.011.048.00014 (Box 48)
        Volume 1.
      - Farnsworth building register of operations, 1950-07-28 -- 1951-06-25; MS099.004.011.048.00015 (Box 48)
        Volume 2.
      - Farnsworth building register of operations, 1951-06-25 -- 1952-02-29; MS099.004.011.049.00001 (Box 49)
        Volume 3.